{
  "meta": {
    "task_id": 32513,
    "project_id": "5395115",
    "status": "COMPLETED",
    "dates": {
      "assigned": "2026-01-11T15:39:27.526000+00:00",
      "completed": "2026-01-11T19:19:19.974000+00:00"
    }
  },
  "topics": {
    "Lower Cabinets": [
      {
        "question": "Lower Cabinets Damaged?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-847167460"
      },
      {
        "question": "Lower Cabinets (linear feet)",
        "answer": 12,
        "type": "number",
        "control_id": "control-447538943"
      },
      {
        "question": "Enter Number of Damaged Lower Boxes",
        "answer": 2,
        "type": "number",
        "control_id": "control-522950290"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are The Lower Cabinets Detached?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-345192616"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are All The Face Frames, Doors, And Drawers Available?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-443878065"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are All The Face Frames, Doors, And Drawer Fronts Damaged?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-526671680"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are The Lower Finished End Panels Damaged?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-297091744"
      },
      {
        "question": "Captured Lower Cabinet Box",
        "answer": [
          96269558
        ],
        "type": "image",
        "control_id": "control-468957161"
      },
      {
        "question": "Captured Lower Face Frames, Doors, and Drawers",
        "answer": [
          96269569,
          96269570,
          96269571
        ],
        "type": "image",
        "control_id": "control-605381080"
      },
      {
        "question": "Is there lower cabinet end panel damage?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-164365889"
      },
      {
        "question": "Captured Lower Cabinet End Panels",
        "answer": [
          96269577
        ],
        "type": "image",
        "control_id": "control-125170752"
      },
      {
        "question": "Select Lower Cabinet Counter Type",
        "answer": "Granite",
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-921852144"
      },
      {
        "question": "If multiple counter types are present, please list the additional types here",
        "answer": "there are not multiple counter types ",
        "type": "text",
        "control_id": "control-590306500"
      }
    ],
    "Upper Cabinets": [
      {
        "question": "Upper Cabinets Damaged?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-601700553"
      },
      {
        "question": "Upper Cabinets (linear feet)",
        "answer": 12,
        "type": "number",
        "control_id": "control-537100044"
      },
      {
        "question": "Enter Number of Damaged Upper Boxes",
        "answer": 3,
        "type": "number",
        "control_id": "control-522950290"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are The Upper Cabinets Detached?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-345192616"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are All The Face Frames, Doors, And Drawers Available?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-443878065"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are All The Face Frames, Doors, And Drawer Fronts Damaged?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-526671680"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are The Upper Finished End Panels Damaged?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-297091744"
      },
      {
        "question": "Captured Upper Cabinet Box",
        "answer": [
          96269586
        ],
        "type": "image",
        "control_id": "control-468957161"
      },
      {
        "question": "Captured Upper Face Frames, Doors, and Drawers",
        "answer": [
          96269587
        ],
        "type": "image",
        "control_id": "control-605381080"
      },
      {
        "question": "Is there upper cabinet end panel damage?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-644175216"
      },
      {
        "question": "Captured Upper Cabinet End Panels",
        "answer": [
          96269590
        ],
        "type": "image",
        "control_id": "control-125170752"
      }
    ],
    "Full Height / Pantry": [
      {
        "question": "Full Height Cabinets Damaged?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-356566833"
      },
      {
        "question": "Enter Number of Damaged Full Height Boxes",
        "answer": 2,
        "type": "number",
        "control_id": "control-522950290"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are The Full Height Cabinets Detached?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-345192616"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are All The Face Frames, Doors, And Drawers Available?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-443878065"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are All The Face Frames, Doors, And Drawer Fronts Damaged?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-526671680"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are the Full Height Finished End Panels Damaged?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-297091744"
      },
      {
        "question": "Captured Full Height/Pantry Cabinets",
        "answer": [
          96269619,
          96269620,
          96269621
        ],
        "type": "image",
        "control_id": "control-468957161"
      },
      {
        "question": "Captured Full Height/Pantry Face Frames, Doors, and Drawers",
        "answer": [
          96272024
        ],
        "type": "image",
        "control_id": "control-605381080"
      },
      {
        "question": "Captured Full Height/Pantry End Panels",
        "answer": [
          96272030
        ],
        "type": "image",
        "control_id": "control-125170752"
      }
    ],
    "Island Cabinets": [
      {
        "question": "Island Cabinets Damaged?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-665202043"
      },
      {
        "question": "Island Cabinets (linear feet)",
        "answer": 12,
        "type": "number",
        "control_id": "control-197971477"
      },
      {
        "question": "Enter Number of Damaged Island Boxes",
        "answer": 2,
        "type": "number",
        "control_id": "control-522950290"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are The Island Cabinets Detached?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-345192616"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are All The Face Frames, Doors, And Drawers Available?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-443878065"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are All The Face Frames, Doors, And Drawer Fronts Damaged?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-526671680"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are the Island Finished End Panels Damaged?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-297091744"
      },
      {
        "question": "Captured Island Cabinet Box",
        "answer": [
          96272039,
          96272040,
          96272041
        ],
        "type": "image",
        "control_id": "control-468957161"
      },
      {
        "question": "Captured Island Face Frames, Doors, and Drawers",
        "answer": [
          96272045
        ],
        "type": "image",
        "control_id": "control-605381080"
      },
      {
        "question": "Is there island cabinet end panel damage?",
        "answer": true,
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-160151579"
      },
      {
        "question": "Captured Island Cabinet End Panels",
        "answer": [
          96272051
        ],
        "type": "image",
        "control_id": "control-125170752"
      },
      {
        "question": "Select Island Cabinet Counter Type",
        "answer": "Granite",
        "type": "option",
        "control_id": "control-921852144"
      }
    ],
    "General": [
      {
        "question": "Full-Height Cabinets (linear feet)",
        "answer": 12,
        "type": "number",
        "control_id": "control-370033639"
      },
      {
        "question": "Enter Damaged Description",
        "answer": "lots of water melted my cabinets",
        "type": "text",
        "control_id": "control-335215653"
      },
      {
        "question": "Upload Overview Photo(s)",
        "answer": [
          96269553,
          96269554
        ],
        "type": "image",
        "control_id": "control-110496963"
      },
      {
        "question": "Now that you have been through the process, please provide any other details that you think would be relevant to the cabinet damage",
        "answer": "no thanks ",
        "type": "text",
        "control_id": "control-500380825"
      }
    ],
    "Countertops": [
      {
        "question": "Countertops (linear feet)",
        "answer": 12,
        "type": "number",
        "control_id": "control-469691344"
      }
    ]
  }
}